couponconnections.com 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Coupon Connections

Our goal at Coupon Connections is to help you and your family save money. We offer our services to you as a reader for free, however there are times when we use referral links.  Some of these are easy to see (like ads in the sidebar) and some are not. Read below for our description of how we collect, use, and store data to help make the experience on our website better. 

The privacy of our visitors to Couponconnections.com is important to us.

At Couponconnections.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Couponconnections.com, and how we safeguard your information. 

**We never sell your personal information to third parties.**

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on Couponconnections.com  to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx ](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Affiliate links and offers: 

Some of the deals and coupons featured on the site are purchased by our staff and some are not.

When we come across a {HOT} deal, we do try to find a way to be compensated first through the manufacturer, company or promoter. Here are the ways we sometimes make money:

**::Affiliate Links-** Some are paid per click, email submission, sign-up, print a coupon, buy a product offer or service.  

**::Campaigns or Sponsored Content-** From time to time Coupon Connections is asked to review and try out a product or service.  We are either compensated or given free product.  We only do this when we feel this is a valuable resource to readers as well because we are always willing to share true and honest opinions.

**::Referral Credits-** There are times when we will receive a referral credit when a reader signs-up using my referral link or purchase of a product.

**::Advertising Images-** On the right side bar is ad space which we are compensated per click or a monthly fee.

The revenue made on this site covers fees to create and maintain it.   It also compensates our staff’s time that we put into writing the content and featuring deals.  Please assume that all links are affiliates or referrals and compensate us in some form.  If you want to use a different link or go straight to the manufacturer please do.

Even though we receive compensation for posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely that of our staff’s. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.
